[{"sentence":"Hello.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":0,"answers":[{"answer":"안녕하세요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"잘가요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"감사합니다.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"Nice to meet you.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":1,"answers":[{"answer":"내일 봐요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"정말 고마워요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"만나서 반가워요.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"Thank you.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":2,"answers":[{"answer":"고마워요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"안녕.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"잘자요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"좋은 아침.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"안녕하세요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":3,"answers":[{"answer":"Hello.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"Good bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thanks.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"감사합니다.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":4,"answers":[{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Hello.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"만나서 반가워요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":5,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Nice to meet you.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"좋은 아침.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":6,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Nice to meet you.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"잘가요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":7,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Nice to meet you.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"잘자요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":8,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Nice to meet you.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"환영합니다.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":9,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Welcome.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"I.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":10,"answers":[{"answer":"나.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"여자.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"그.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"You.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":11,"answers":[{"answer":"나.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"남자.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"너.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"Apple.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":12,"answers":[{"answer":"먹다.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"사과.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"아기.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"Eat.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":13,"answers":[{"answer":"마셔요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"여자.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"먹어요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"소년.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"나.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":14,"answers":[{"answer":"You.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Boy.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"너.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":15,"answers":[{"answer":"You.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"Apple.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Boy.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"빵.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":16,"answers":[{"answer":"You.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Apple.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bread.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"먹어요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":17,"answers":[{"answer":"Buy.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Eat.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"You.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"나는 사과를 먹어요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":18,"answers":[{"answer":"I drink coffee.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I am a boy.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I eat apple.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"You eat apple.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"You eat Bread!","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":19,"answers":[{"answer":"나는 빵을 먹어요!","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나는 주스를 마셔요!","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"너는 사과를 먹어!","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"너는 빵을 먹어!","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"He.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":20,"answers":[{"answer":"그녀.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"남자.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"그.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"She.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":21,"answers":[{"answer":"그녀.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"여자.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"Coffee.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":22,"answers":[{"answer":"커피.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"그녀.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"사과.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"안녕.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"Drink.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":23,"answers":[{"answer":"마셔요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"사과.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"그녀.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"먹어요.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"그는.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":24,"answers":[{"answer":"She.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Boy.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Eat.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"He.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"그녀는.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":25,"answers":[{"answer":"Woman.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"She.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"Girl.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"물.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":26,"answers":[{"answer":"Boy.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Coffee.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Water.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"Apple.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"마셔요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":27,"answers":[{"answer":"Buy.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Drink.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Eat.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"그녀는 커피를 마셔요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":28,"answers":[{"answer":"He goes to Apple.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"She drinks coffee.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"She eats an apple.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"He drinks water.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":29,"answers":[{"answer":"소년은 물를 마신다.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"그녀는 물를 마신다.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"그는 물를 마신다.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"나는 물를 마신다.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"We.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":30,"answers":[{"answer":"그.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"나.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"우리.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"They.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":31,"answers":[{"answer":"그녀.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"그.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"그들.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"우리.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"Go.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":32,"answers":[{"answer":"간다.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"마신다.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"신문.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"물.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"School.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":33,"answers":[{"answer":"학교.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"커피.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"사과.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"극장.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"우리.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":34,"answers":[{"answer":"They.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"We.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"me.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"You.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"그들.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":35,"answers":[{"answer":"We.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"They.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"He.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"간다.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":36,"answers":[{"answer":"Good.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Go.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"Book.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Eat.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"극장.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":37,"answers":[{"answer":"Cinema.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"Newspaper.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"School.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Eat.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"우리는 학교에 가요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":38,"answers":[{"answer":"We go to the school.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"We go to the cinema.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"We com to the school.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"They go to the school.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"They go to cinema.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":39,"answers":[{"answer":"그들은 학교에 가요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"그들은 공항에 가요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"우리는 극장에 가요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"그들은 극장에 가요.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"Boy.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":40,"answers":[{"answer":"극장.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"소년.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"Girl.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":41,"answers":[{"answer":"책.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"학교.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"소녀.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"Man.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":42,"answers":[{"answer":"읽다.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"남자.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"먹다.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"뉴스.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"Woman.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":43,"answers":[{"answer":"본다.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"읽는다.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"여자.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"않읽는다.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"소년.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":44,"answers":[{"answer":"School.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Boy.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"He.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Here.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"소녀.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":45,"answers":[{"answer":"Girl.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"Move.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Drink.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Sea.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"남자.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":46,"answers":[{"answer":"Woman.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Man.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"Girl.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Boy.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"여자.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":47,"answers":[{"answer":"See.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Man.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Girl.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Woman.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"나는 남자다.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":48,"answers":[{"answer":"I am a boy.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I am a man.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"I am a girl.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"I am a Woman.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"I am a girl.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":49,"answers":[{"answer":"저는 여자에요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"저는 남자에요.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"저는 소녀에요.","isCorrect":true},{"answer":"저는 소년이에요.","isCorrect":false}]},{"sentence":"아이.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":50,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"엄마.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":51,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"아빠.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":52,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"사랑해요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":53,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"Child.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":54,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"Mom.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":55,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"Dad.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":56,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"Love.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":57,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"Child loves mom.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":58,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"아빠는 엄마를 사랑해요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":59,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"아기.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":60,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"장난감.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":61,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"우유.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":62,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"좋아해요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":63,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"Baby.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":64,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"Toy.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":65,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"Milk.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":66,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"Like.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":67,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"아기는 장난감을 좋아해요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":68,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"Baby likes milk.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":69,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"내 친구.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":70,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"샤워.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":71,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"공부.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":72,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"싫어해요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":73,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"My friend.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":74,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"Shower. ","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":75,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"Study.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":76,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"Hate.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":77,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"My friend hate showers.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":78,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"내 친구는 공부를 싫어해요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":79,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"오빠(형).","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":80,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"버스.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":81,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"택시.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":82,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"타요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":83,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"My brother.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":84,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"Bus.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":85,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"Taxi.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":86,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"Take.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":87,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"형이 버스를 타요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":88,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"My brother is take a taxi.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":89,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"언니(누나)","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":90,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"책.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":91,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"신문.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":92,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"읽어요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":93,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"My sister.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":94,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"Book.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":95,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"Newspaper.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":96,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"Read.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":97,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"누나가 책을 읽어요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":98,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"My sister read a newspaper.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":99,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"Boss.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":100,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"그리고.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":101,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"하지만.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":102,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"~때문에.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":103,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"만약.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":104,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"And.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":105,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"But.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":106,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"Becouse.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":107,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"Boss.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":108,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"Boss.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":109,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"닭고기.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":110,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"돼지고기.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":111,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"소고기.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":112,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"안 먹어요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":113,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"Chicken.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":114,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"Pork.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":115,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"Beef.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":116,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"Don't eat.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":117,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"나는 닭 고기를 안 먹어요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":118,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"I do not eat pork.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":119,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"오렌지 주스.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":120,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"파인애플.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":121,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"수박.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":122,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"맥주.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":123,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"Orange juice.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":124,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"Pineapple.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":125,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"Watermelon.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":126,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"Beer.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":127,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"I don't drink orange juice.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":128,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"나는 맥주 안마셔요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":129,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"극장.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":130,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"쇼핑몰.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":131,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"시장.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":132,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"회사.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":133,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"Cinema.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":134,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"Shoping mall.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":135,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"Mart.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":136,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"Office.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":137,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"I don't go to cinema.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":138,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"난 시장에 안가요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":139,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"학생.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":140,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"선생님.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":141,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"운전기사.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":142,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"손님.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":143,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"Student. ","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":144,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"Teacher.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":145,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"Driver.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":146,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"Customer.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":147,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"I am not student.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":148,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"전 손님이 아니에요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":149,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"남자친구.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":150,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"여자친구.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":151,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"있어요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":152,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"없어요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":153,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"Boyfriend.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":154,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"Girlfriend.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":155,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"Have.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":156,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"Don't have.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":157,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"남자친구가 없어요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":158,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"I don't have Girlfriend.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":159,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"안 사요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":160,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"안 팔아요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":161,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"안 봐요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":162,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"안 만들어요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":163,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"안 놀아요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":164,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"Don't buy.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":165,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"Don't sell.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":166,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"Don't see.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":167,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"Don't make.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":168,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"Don't play.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":169,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"하다. 해요. 할.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":170,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"안 하다. 안 해요. 안 할.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":171,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"할 수 있다.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":172,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"할 수 없다.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":173,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"Do.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":174,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"Do not.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":175,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"Can.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":176,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"Con not.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":177,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"I can do it.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":178,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"우리는 운동을 해요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":179,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"네.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":180,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"아니요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":181,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"좋아요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":182,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"괜찬아요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":183,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"맞아요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":184,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"Yes.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":185,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"No.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":186,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"OK.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":187,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"No thanks.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":188,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"Right.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":189,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"하지마!","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":190,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"먹지마!","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":191,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"만지지마!","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":192,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"가지마!","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":193,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"자지마!","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":194,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"Do not!","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":195,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"Do not eat!","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":196,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"Do not touch!","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":197,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"Do not go!","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":198,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"Do not be sleep!","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":199,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"Boss. 오늘.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":200,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"내일.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":201,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"어제.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":202,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"지금.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":203,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"다음에.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":204,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"주.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":205,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"월.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":206,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"년.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":207,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"이번주. 이번달. 올해.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":208,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"지난주. 지난달. 작년. 다음주. 다음달. 내년.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":209,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"아침.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":210,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"점심.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":211,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"저녁.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":212,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"지금.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":213,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"Breakfast.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":214,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"Lunch.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":215,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"Dinner.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":216,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"Now.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":217,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"Do you eat breakfast now?","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":218,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"저녁 먹니?","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":219,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"학교.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":220,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"회사.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":221,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"병원.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":222,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"커피숍.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":223,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"School.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":224,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"Company.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":225,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"Hospital.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":226,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"Coffee shop.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":227,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"Are you going to school now?","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":228,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"병원가니?","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":229,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"나를.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":230,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"너를.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":231,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"그를.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":232,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"그녀를.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":233,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"me.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":234,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"you.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":235,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"him.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":236,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"her.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":237,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"그가 나를 사랑하니?","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":238,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"Does she love you?","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":239,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"미국.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":240,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"중국.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":241,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"한국.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":242,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"일본.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":243,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"Indonesia.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":244,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"India.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":245,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"England.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":246,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"Russia.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":247,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"그들은 한국을 좋아하니?","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":248,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"그녀는 미국을 좋아하니?","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":249,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"덥니?","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":250,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"춥니?","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":251,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"따뜻하니?","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":252,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"ㅂ따뜻하니?","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":253,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"Is it Hot?","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":254,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"Is it Cold?","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":255,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"Is it Warm?","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":256,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"Is it Cool?","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":257,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"Is it cold there?","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":258,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"이건 따뜻하니?","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":259,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"배고프니?","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":260,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"배부르니?","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":261,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"목마르니?","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":262,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"맛있니?","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":263,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"Are you hungry?","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":264,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"Are you full?","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":265,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"Thirsty?","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":266,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"Do you like it?","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":267,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"먹을래?","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":268,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"Do you want eat?","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":269,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"졸리니?","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":270,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"심심하니?","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":271,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"재미있니?","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":272,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"기쁘니?","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":273,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"자니?","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":274,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"Are you sleepy?","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":275,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"Are you bored?","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":276,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"Are you having fun?","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":277,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"Are you happy?","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":278,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"Are you sleeping?","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":279,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"멋있니?","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":280,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"잘생겼니?","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":281,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"못생겼니?","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":282,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"귀엽니?","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":283,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"괜찬니?","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":284,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"Is it cool?","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":285,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"Is is handsome?","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":286,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"Is it ugly?","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":287,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"Is is cute?","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":288,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"Are you okay?","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":289,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"숙제 하니?","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":290,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"공부 하니?","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":291,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"운동 하니?","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":292,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"일 하니?","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":293,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"쇼핑 하니?","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":294,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"Do you do your homework?","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":295,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"Do you study?","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":296,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"Do you exercise?","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":297,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"Do you work?","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":298,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"Do you shop?","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":299,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"Boss. 언제.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":300,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"어디서.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":301,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"무엇을.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":302,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"어떻게.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":303,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"누가.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":304,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"왜.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":305,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"When.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":306,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"Where.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":307,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"What.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":308,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"How.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":309,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"일.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":310,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"이.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":311,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"삼.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":312,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"사.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":313,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"오.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":314,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"육.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":315,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"칠.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":316,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"팔.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":317,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"구.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":318,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"십.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":319,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"십일.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":320,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"십이.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":321,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"십삼.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":322,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"십사.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":323,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"십오.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":324,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"십육.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":325,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"십칠.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":326,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"십팔.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":327,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"십구.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":328,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"이십.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":329,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":330,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"백.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":331,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"이백.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":332,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"삼백.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":333,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"사백.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":334,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"오백.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":335,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"육백.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":336,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"칠백.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":337,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"팔백.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":338,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"구백.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":339,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"천.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":340,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"만.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":341,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"이만.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":342,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"삼만.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":343,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"사만.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":344,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"오만.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":345,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"육만.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":346,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"칠만.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":347,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"팔만.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":348,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"구만.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":349,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"억.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":350,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"하나.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":351,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"둘.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":352,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"셋.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":353,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"넷.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":354,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"다섯.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":355,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"여섯.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":356,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"일곱.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":357,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"여덜.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":358,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"아홉.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":359,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"열.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":360,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"열하나.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":361,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"열둘.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":362,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"열셋.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":363,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"열넷.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":364,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"열다섯.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":365,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"열여섯.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":366,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"열일곱.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":367,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"열여덞.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":368,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"열아홉.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":369,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"스물.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":370,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"스물하나.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":371,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"스물둘.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":372,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"스물셋.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":373,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"스물넷.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":374,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"스물다섯.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":375,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"스물여섯.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":376,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"스물일곱.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":377,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"스물여덞.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":378,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"스물아홉.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":379,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"서른.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":380,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"1000 원.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":381,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"10 개.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":382,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"1 월.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":383,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"만원.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":384,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"백개.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":385,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"12월.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":386,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"100,000 won.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":387,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"In March.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":388,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"thousand.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":389,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"한번.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":390,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"한개.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":391,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"한 개 더.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":392,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"한 개 만.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":393,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"한번만.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":394,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"Ten times.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":395,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"Ten more.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":396,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"Only ten.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":397,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"Only one mere.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":398,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"Just a bite. ","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":399,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"보스. ","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":400,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":401,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":402,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":403,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":404,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":405,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":406,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":407,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":408,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":409,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"먹을거에요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":410,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":411,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":412,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":413,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":414,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":415,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":416,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":417,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":418,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":419,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"먹을거에요?","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":420,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":421,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":422,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":423,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":424,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":425,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":426,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":427,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":428,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":429,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"안 먹을거에요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":430,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":431,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":432,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":433,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":434,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":435,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":436,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":437,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":438,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":439,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"먹었어요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":440,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":441,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":442,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":443,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":444,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":445,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":446,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":447,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":448,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":449,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"먹었어요?","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":450,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":451,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":452,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":453,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":454,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":455,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":456,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":457,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":458,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":459,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"안먹었어요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":460,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":461,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":462,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":463,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":464,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":465,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":466,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":467,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":468,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":469,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"먹는중이에요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":470,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":471,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":472,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":473,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":474,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":475,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":476,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":477,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":478,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":479,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"먹는중이에요?","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":480,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":481,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":482,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":483,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":484,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":485,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":486,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":487,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":488,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":489,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"먹는중이었어요.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":490,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":491,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":492,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":493,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":494,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":495,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":496,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":497,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":498,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":499,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"보스.","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":500,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":501,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":502,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":503,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":504,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":505,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":506,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":507,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":508,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]},{"sentence":"","question":"Translate this sentence.","id":509,"answers":[{"answer":"Good night.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Bye.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Thank you.","isCorrect":false},{"answer":"Good morning.","isCorrect":true}]}]